A Guide to the Population Council records, Accession 1, RG 1 FA210
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 1, 1
  - Grant Files, 1958-1966; 2
    - Grant # M64.61 - University of Pennsylvania: Neural Control Studies (Box 58, Folder 961)
    - Grant # M64.62 - Inst. of Psychiatry, Eng.: Luteinizing Hormone Releasing Factor (Box 58, Folder 962)
    - Grant # M64.63 - University of British Columbia: Anti-Estrogenic Compounds (Box 58, Folder 963)
    - Grant # M64.64 - University of Milan, Italy: Endocrine Studies (Box 58, Folder 964)
    - Grant # M64.64 - University of Oxford: Anti-Fertility Agents Study (Box 58, Folder 965)
    - Grant # M64.66 - University of Uppsala: Gonadotrophin Studies (Box 58, Folder 966)
    - Grant # M64.67 - Weizmann Inst. of Science, Israel: Gonadotrophin Studies (Box 58, Folder 967)
    - Grant # M64.68 - Clinica Obstetrica, University of Chile: Effects of Gestagens (Box 58, Folder 968)
    - Grant # M64.69 - NYU: Ovulatory Suppressants Studies (Box 58, Folder 969)
    - Grant # M64.70 - University of Liverpool: Gamete Studies (Box 58, Folder 970)
    - Grant # M64.71 - Free Hospital for Women, Mass.: Embryo Development Studies (Box 58, Folder 971)
    - Grant # M64.72 - Karolinska Inst., Sweden: Seminal Fluid Studies (Box 58, Folder 972)
    - Grant # M64.73 - Vanderbilt University: Sperm Passage Studies (Box 58, Folder 973)
    - Grant # M64.74 - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, NY: Human Ejaculate Studies (Box 58, Folder 974)
    - Grant # D64.75 - Consejo Nacional de Planificacin...: Population Study of San Salvador (Box 59, Folder 975-976)
    - Grant # T64.76 - U.S. Armed Forces: Prototypic Family Planning Programs (Box 59, Folder 977)
    - Grant # T64.77 - Ministry of Public Health and Social Assistance, Tunisia: Resident Advisor (Box 59, Folder 978-979)
    - Grant # T64.78 - National Research Council, Thailand: Resident Advisor (Box 59, Folder 980)
    - Grant # D64.79 - CERES, Tunisia: Training Program (Box 59, Folder 981-982)
    - Grant # D64.80 - Jadavpur University, India: Demographic Research Unit (Box 59, Folder 983-984)
    - Grant # D64.81 - Seoul National University, Korea: Field Study of Fertility Trends and Differentials (Box 59, Folder 985)
    - Grant # D64.82 - Korean Statistical Assoc.: 1960 Korean Population Study (Box 59, Folder 986)
    - Grant # D64.83 - American Assembly, Columbia University: Pan-American Conference on the Population Dilemma (Box 59, Folder 987-989)
    - Grant # D64.84 - U.N. - CELADE, Chile: Operation of CELADE in Santiago (Box 60, Folder 990-991)
    - Grant # D64.85 - University of Los Andes, Colombia: Salary Expenditures for Demographic Program (Box 60, Folder 992-993)
    - Grant # D64.86 - Universidad del Valle, Colombia: Research Program in Population Problems (Box 60, Folder 994-996)
    - Grant # D64.87 - University of Pittsburgh: Post-Doctoral Research Residency (Box 60, Folder 997-998)
    - Grant # D64.88 - Georgetown University: Attitudes of Catholic Couples in the U.S. (Box 60, Folder 999-1000)
    - Grant # D64.89 - St. Louis University: Catholic Thinking on Human Sexuality (Box 60, Folder 1001)
    - Grant # T64.91 - PPFK (Korea): Family Planning National Training and Educational Program (Box 60, Folder 1002-1004)
    - Grant # M64.92 - Columbia University: Cytological Changes with use of IUD (Box 61, Folder 1005)
    - Grant # M64.93 - JCRR, Taiwan: Medical Follow-up Study on IUD Cases (Box 61, Folder 1006)
    - Grant # M64.94 - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, NY: Continuation of Clinical Study of IUCD's (Box 61, Folder 1007)
    - Grant # M64.95 - Medical College of Georgia: Histochemical Changes and Hormone Assays (Box 61, Folder 1008)
    - Grant # M64.96 - Medical Research Foundation of Oregon, Inc.: Research on IUCD's (Box 61, Folder 1009)
    - Grant # M64.97 - Midwest Foundation for Research and Education, Ohio: Endocrine Evaluation of the Menstrual Cycle with the IUD (Box 61, Folder 1010)
    - Grant # M64.98 - NYU Medical Center: Comparative Study of IUD's (Box 61, Folder 1011)
    - Grant # M64.99 - Ohio State University: Clinical and Laboratory Evaluation of IUD (Box 61, Folder 1012)
    - Grant # M64.100 - Pennsylvania Hospital: Brush Endometrial Smears in Presence of IUCD's (Box 61, Folder 1013)
    - Grant # M64.101 - Planned Parenthood Center, Los Angeles: Research on Contraceptive Effectiveness (Box 61, Folder 1014)
    - Grant # M64.102 - Teheran University, Iran: IUD Evaluation (Box 61, Folder 1015)
    - Grant # M64.103 - Temple University: Tailless Margulies Spiral Studies (Box 61, Folder 1016)
    - Grant # M64.104 - Consejo Nacional de Investigaciones... Argentina: Gonadotrophin Studies (Box 61, Folder 1017)
    - Grant # M64.105 - Dalhousie University, Nova Scotia: Mechanism of Implantation (Box 61, Folder 1018)
    - Grant # M64.106 - Guy's Hospital Medical School, Eng.: Effects of Drugs on Pregnancy Studies (Box 61, Folder 1019)
    - Grant # M64.107 - Hebrew University, Israel: Auditory Stimuli Effect on Reproductive Processes (Box 61, Folder 1020)
    - Grant # M64.108 - Hokkaido University, Japan: Ovulation Prediction Studies (Box 61, Folder 1021)
    - Grant # M64.109 - Inst. de Histologia y Embriologia, Argentina: Mechanism of Sperm Release Studies (Box 61, Folder 1022)
    - Grant # M64.110 - Kumamoto University, Japan: Immunologic Induction of Fertility (Box 61, Folder 1023)
    - Grant # M64.111 - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, NY: Establishment of a Cytological Laboratory (Box 61, Folder 1024)
    - Grant # M64.112 - Universidad Catlica de Chile: Substances Obtained from Human Brain (Box 61, Folder 1025)
    - Grant # M64.113 - University of Birmingham, Eng.: Gonadal Studies (Box 61, Folder 1026)
    - Grant # M64.114 - University of Bristol, Eng.: Ultrastructure of Human Anterior Pituitary (Box 61, Folder 1027)
    - Grant # M64.115 - University of Sydney, Australia: Effects of Estrogens on Early Pregnancy (Box 61, Folder 1028)
    - Grant # M64.116 - University of Perugia, Italy: Enzymes in Semen (Box 61, Folder 1029)
    - Grant # M64.117 - University of Tokyo: Hypothalamus-Hypophysial-Ovarian Function Control (Box 61, Folder 1030)
    - Grant # M64.118 - Weizmann Inst. of Science, Israel: Mechanism of Nidation (Box 61, Folder 1031)
    - Grant # M64.119 - Worcester Foundation, for Experimental Biology: Sperm Physiology Studies (Box 61, Folder 1032)
    - Grant # M64.120 - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Carbonic Anhydrase and Implantation Inhibition Studies (Box 61, Folder 1033)
    - Grant # M64.121 - N.I.H. (U.S.): Motility and Energy Metabolism (Box 61, Folder 1034)
    - Grant # D64.123 - U.N. - CELADE, Chile: Fertility Studies in Ecuador (Box 61, Folder 1035)
    - Book and Equipment Fund, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 1036)
    - Grant # T65.1 - Manila Health Department: Project on Family Planning (Box 61, Folder 1037-1038)
    - Grant # D65.2 - American Eugenics Society: General Purposes (Box 61, Folder 1039)
    - Grant # D65.3: Program in Genetics and Population Characteristics (Box 61, Folder 1040-1041)
    - Grant # D65.4 - University of Athens, Greece: Mechanical Tabulation Equipment Mass Communication with Reference to Family Planning (Box 61, Folder 1042)
    - Grant # D65.5 - University of Chicago (Box 61, Folder 1043)
    - Grant # D65.6 - IUSSP, Belgium: Support of the 1965 World Population Conference (Box 61, Folder 1044)
    - Grant # D65.7 - IUSSP, Belgium: General Purposes (Box 61, Folder 1045)
    - Grant # D65.8 - United Nations: Support of DTRC in Cairo, U.A.R. Family Planning Action and Research Program (Box 62, Folder 1046)
    - Grant # T65.10 - JCRR, Taiwan (Box 62, Folder 1047)
    - Grant # T65.11 - Yonsei University, Korea: Family Planning Studies (Box 62, Folder 1048)
    - Grant # T65.12 - PPFK (Korea): Family Planning Education for Medical and Nursing Students (Box 62, Folder 1049)
    - Grant # T65.13 - Ministry of Health, India: Support for Family Planning Program (Box 62, Folder 1050-1051)
    - Grant # T65.14 - International Conf. on Family Planning Programs, Switzerland: Expenses (Box 62, Folder 1052)
    - Grant # T65.15 - University of California, Berkeley: Public Health Education Research Project at Dacca, East Pakistan (Box 62, Folder 1053)
    - Grant # T65.16: Acquisition of Patent Rights for IUD's (Box 62, Folder 1054)
    - Grant # M65.17 - Facult de Mdicine de Paris: Metabolic Pathways Study (Box 62, Folder 1055)
    - Grant # M65.18 - Gunma University, Japan: Hypothalamic Factors Controlling Gonadotrophin Release (Box 62, Folder 1056)
    - Grant # M65.19 - University of Washington: Urinary Inorganic Iodide Excretion Studies (Box 62, Folder 1057)
    - Grant # M65.20 - Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation, Calif.: Hormone Studies (Box 62, Folder 1058)
    - Grant # M65.21 - Columbia University: Mode of Action Malucidin Studies (Box 62, Folder 1059)
    - Grant # M65.22 - Consejo Nacional de Investigaciones...Argentina: Immunological Studies (Box 62, Folder 1060)
    - Grant # M65.23 - University of Chile: Physiology of the Uterine Cervix (Box 62, Folder 1061)
    - Grant # M65.24 - McGill University, Canada: Endocrine Control Investigations (Box 62, Folder 1062)
    - Grant # M65.25 - University of Kansas: Steroid Interactions Studies (Box 62, Folder 1063)
    - Grant # M65.26 - Catholic Marriage Advisory Council, Eng.: Basal Body Temperature Study (Box 62, Folder 1064)
    - Grant # M65.27 - NCMH: IUD Cooperative Statistical Program (Box 62, Folder 1065)
    - Grant # M65.28 - University of Michigan: Human Uterine Muscle Physiology Studies (Box 62, Folder 1066)
    - Grant # M65.29 - Victoria Jubilee Hospital, Jamaica: IUD's in Postpartum Patients (Box 62, Folder 1067)
    - Grant # M65.30 - University of Bahia, Brazil: Contraceptive Devices (Box 62, Folder 1068)
    - Grant # M65.31 - Vanderbilt University: Endometrial Response to IUD's (Box 62, Folder 1069)
    - Grant # M65.32 - Johns Hopkins University: Improvement of IUD Design (Box 62, Folder 1070)
    - Grant # M65.33 - Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn: Early Puerperal Insertion of IUD's (Box 62, Folder 1071)
    - Grant # D65.34 - University of Chile: Contraception Use and Effect (Box 62, Folder 1072-1073)
    - Grant # M65.35: Film on Physiology of Reproduction (Box 62, Folder 1074)
    - Grant # D65.36 - IUSSP, Belgium: Expenses of Participants in World Population Conference (Box 62, Folder 1075)
    - Grant # D65.37 - Ministry of Health and Social Affairs, Korea: Demographic Advisor (Box 62, Folder 1076-1077)
    - Grant # D65.38 - University of the Philippines: Services of a Visiting Professor of Demography (Box 63, Folder 1078)
    - Grant # D65.39 - JCRR, Taiwan: Demographic Fact Book (Box 63, Folder 1079)
    - Grant # D65.40 - Pakistan Academy for Rural Development: Demographic Analyst, Advisors, and Equipment (Box 63, Folder 1080-1081)
    - Grant # D65.41 - Middle East Technical University, Turkey: Demographic Training and Research Program (Box 63, Folder 1082-1083)
    - Grant # D65.42 - Ministry of Education, Turkey: Support of Turkish Fertility (Box 63, Folder 1084)
    - Grant # D65.43 - University College, Kenya: Teaching and Research in Demography (Box 63, Folder 1085)
    - Grant # D65.44 - University of Ibadan, Nigeria: African Population Conference (Box 63, Folder 1086-1088)
    - Grant # D65.45 - University of Sao Paulo, Brazil: Fertility and Abortion Survey (Box 63, Folder 1089)
    - Grant # D65.46 - Instituto Torcuato Di Tella, Argentina: Census Monographs (Box 63, Folder 1090-1091)
    - Grant # D65.47 - Inst. of International Education, CHEAR: Support for Inter-American Seminar (Box 64, Folder 1092-1093)
    - Grant # D65.48 - Princeton University: Demographic Research (Box 64, Folder 1094-1095)
    - Grant # T65.49 - Queen Elizabeth Hospital, West Indies: Demographic and Cytological Effects of an IUD Program (Box 64, Folder 1096-1097)
    - Grant # T65.50 - National Research Council, Thailand: Family Planning Pilot Project (Box 64, Folder 1098-1100)
    - Grant # T65.51 - University of Puerto Rico: Contraceptive Users Studies (Box 64, Folder 1101-1102)
    - Grant # T65.52 - Ministry of Health and Social Welfare, Korea: Provide Medical Advisor (Box 64, Folder 1103)
    - Grant # T65.53 - PPFK (Korea): Induced Abortion Studies in Rural Area (Box 64, Folder 1104)
    - Grant # M65.54 - University of Chile: Distribution of Genetic Characters (Box 64, Folder 1105)
    - Grant # M65.55 - V.A. Hospital, California (Long Beach): Hormonal Regulation Studies (Box 64, Folder 1106)
    - Grant # M65.56 - University of Oxford: Antifertility Agents Studies (Box 64, Folder 1107)
    - Grant # M65.57 - Clinica Obstetrica,. University of Chile: Effect of Gestagens (Box 64, Folder 1108)
    - Grant # M65.58 - Consejo Nacional de Investigaciones... Argentina: Estrogen/Progesterone Studies (Box 64, Folder 1109)
    - Grant # M65.59 - NYU Medical School: Ovulatory Suppressants Study (Box 64, Folder 1110)
    - Grant # M65.61 - Tohoku University, Japan: Uterine Mucosubstance Studies (Box 64, Folder 1111)
    - Grant # M65.62 - Cornell University: Antifertility Compounds Action (Box 64, Folder 1112)
    - Grant # M65.63 - Karolinska Inst., Sweden: Biochemical Studies (Box 64, Folder 1113)
    - Grant # M65.64 - Temple University: Effects of Nucleic Acids (Box 64, Folder 1114)
    - Grant # M65.66 - University of Liverpool: Transport of Gametes Studies (Box 64, Folder 1115)
    - Grant # M65.67 - Cornell University: Quantitative Cytological Analysis (Box 64, Folder 1116)
    - Grant # M65.68 - Yale University: Ovum Implantation Compounds (Box 64, Folder 1117)
    - Grant # M65.69 - Toho University, Japan: Tubal Occlusion Studies (Box 64, Folder 1118)
    - Grant # M65.70 - University of Pennsylvania: Metabolism and Nutrition of Embryos (Box 64, Folder 1119)
    - Grant # M65.71 - Amer. British Cowdray Hospital, Mexico: IUD Acceptability and Effectiveness (Box 64, Folder 1120)
    - Grant # M65.72 - Cornell University: Intra-Uterine Bows Studies (Box 64, Folder 1121)
    - Grant # M65.73 - Ryder Memorial Hospital, Puerto Rico: IUD Field Study (Box 64, Folder 1122)
    - Grant # M65.74 - University of California - S.F.: Effects of Intra-Uterine Foreign Bodies (Box 64, Folder 1123)
    - Grant # M65.75 - Columbia University: Pelvic Inflammatory Disease (Box 64, Folder 1124)
    - Grant # M65.76 - SUNY: Ultrastructural Effects of IUD's (Box 64, Folder 1125)
    - Grant # M65.77 - University of Colorado: Clinical Investigation of the IUD (Box 64, Folder 1126)
    - Grant # M65.78 - NY Medical College: Effects of IUD Steel Ring (Box 64, Folder 1127)
    - Grant # M65.79 - Columbia University: Subcutaneous and Intra-Uterine Sites Comparison (Box 64, Folder 1128)
    - Grant # M65.80 - Columbia University: Evaluation of IUCD's (Box 64, Folder 1129)
    - Grant # M65.81 - Columbia University: IUD Study at Harlem Hospital Center (Box 64, Folder 1130-1131)
    - Grant # M65.82 - Herman J. Engel, NY: Film on Intra-Uterine Contraception (Box 65, Folder 1132)
    - Grant # T65.83 - Ministry of Health of India: Support of India's National Family Planning Program (Box 65, Folder 1133)
    - Grant # D65.84 - Administrative Expenditure: Latin American Conference (Box 65, Folder 1134)
    - Grant # D65.85 - Administrative Expenditure: Preparation of a Book on Population (Box 65, Folder 1135-1136)
    - Grant # T65.86 - Government of Kenya: Advisory Commission (Box 65, Folder 1137-1138)
    - Grant # T65.87 - Ain Shams University, U.A.R.: Provide Rural IUCD Services (Box 65, Folder 1139-1140)
    - Grant # T65.88 - PPFK (Korea): Two Year Medical IUD Follow-up Studies (Box 65, Folder 1141-1142)
    - Grant # M65.89 - University of Singapore: IUCD Tolerance and Acceptance Study (Box 65, Folder 1143-1144)
    - Grant # M65.90 - Albert Einstein Medical College: IUD Study (Box 65, Folder 1145)
    - Grant # M65.91 - Arkansas State Health Department: Maintenance of State-Wide IUD Program (Box 65, Folder 1146)
    - Grant # M65.92 - JCRR, Taiwan: Training Activities Expansion (Box 65, Folder 1147)
    - Grant # T65.93 - Ministry of Health, India: Lippes Loops and Inserters (Box 65, Folder 1148)
    - Grant # D65.95 - Population Reference Bureau: General Corporate Purposes (Box 65, Folder 1149)
    - Grant # T65.96 - Ministry of Health, Pakistan: Lippes Loops Supplies (Box 65, Folder 1150)
    - Grant # D65.97 - Seoul National University, Korea: Population Research and Training Center (Box 65, Folder 1151-1152)
    - Grant # D65.98 - Princeton University: Interview Responses In Fertility Studies (Box 66, Folder 1153)
    - Grant # D65.99 - Pakistan Inst. of Development Eco.: PGE Project (Box 66, Folder 1154)
    - Grant # D65.100 - CERES, Tunisia: Supplies (Box 66, Folder 1155)
    - Grant # D65.101 - Center for Population Studies, Peru: Support for National Seminar on Population and Development (Box 66, Folder 1156-1157)
    - Grant # D65.102 - Sillman University, Philippines: Research and Action Program in Family Planning (Box 66, Folder 1158-1159)
    - Grant # T65.103 - Manila Health Department: Equipment and Supplies (Box 66, Folder 1160)
    - Grant # T65.104 - PPFK (Korea): Urban Research and Demonstration Project in Family Planning (Box 66, Folder 1161-1162)
    - Grant # T65.105 - Development Fund for Contraceptive Material: Support for Developmental Activities (Box 66, Folder 1163)
    - Grant # T65.106 - JCRR, Taiwan: Follow-up Study of IUD Cases (Box 66, Folder 1164-1165)
    - Grant # T65.107 - Ministry of Public Health..., Tunisia: P.C. Resident Advisor (Box 66, Folder 1166)
    - Grant # T65.108 - Ministry of Health and Social Welfare, Korea: Health Education Resident Advisor (Box 66, Folder 1167)
    - Grant # T65.109 - Ministry of Health and Social Welfare, Pak.: Research and Training (Box 66, Folder 1168-1170)
    - Grant # M65.110 - University of Helsinki, Finland: Hormonal Regulation Studies (Box 66, Folder 1171)
    - Grant # M65.111 - University of Minnesota: Oral Contraceptives (Box 66, Folder 1172)
    - Grant # M65.112 - Consejo Nacional de Investigaciones...Argentina: Diabetes and Reproduction (Box 66, Folder 1173)
    - Grant # M65.113 - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Implantation Inhibition and Antizygotic Agents (Box 66, Folder 1174)
    - Grant # M65.114 - University of California - S.F.: Unexplored Aspects of Vasectomy (Box 66, Folder 1175)
    - Grant # M65.115 - Universidad Catlica de Chile: Puerperium Physiology Study (Box 66, Folder 1176)
    - Grant # M65.116 - Maudsley Hospital, England: Luteinizing Hormone-releasing Factor Study (Box 66, Folder 1177)
    - Grant # M65.117 - University of Tokyo, Japan: Hypothalamus - Hypophyseal-Ovarian Function (Box 67, Folder 1178)
    - Grant # M65.118 - University of Milan, Italy: Neuroendocrine Influence on Puberty (Box 67, Folder 1179)
    - Grant # M65.119 - University of Kansas: Neurohormone - Hypophyseal Gonadotrophins and Steroid Interactions Studies (Box 67, Folder 1180)
    - Grant # M65.120 - Universidad Catlica de Chile: Substances Obtained from Human Brain (Box 67, Folder 1181)
    - Grant # M65.121 - College of Medicine, Taiwan: Endocrinological Study of Pathologic Pregnancies (Box 67, Folder 1182)
    - Grant # M65.122 - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: The Physiology of Sperm and the Effects of Antifertility Compounds (Box 67, Folder 1183)
    - Grant # M65.124 - Inst. de Histologia y Embriologia, Argentina: Mechanism of the Spermiation and Histophysiology (Box 67, Folder 1184)
    - Grant # M65.125 - Servicio de Fisiologicia Obstetrica, Uruguay: Isolation of Endogenous Oxytocin (Box 67, Folder 1185)
    - Grant # M65.126 - Consejo Nacional de Investigaciones...Argentina: Effects of Gonadotrophins (Box 67, Folder 1186)
    - Grant # M65.127 - Asoc. Pro - Maternidad Clinca, Uruguay: Tubal and Uterine Contractility Studies (Box 67, Folder 1187)
    - Grant # M65.128 - Columbia University: Cytological Change in the Cervix (Box 67, Folder 1188)
    - Grant # M65.129 - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, NY: Clinical Study of IUCD's (Box 67, Folder 1189)
    - Grant # M65.130 - NYU Medical Center: Comparative Study on IUD's (Box 67, Folder 1190)
    - Grant # M65.131 - Pennsylvania Hospital: Brush Endometrial Smears (Box 67, Folder 1191)
    - Grant # M65.132 - Planned Parenthood Center, Los Angeles: Contraceptive Effectiveness Research (Box 67, Folder 1192)
    - Grant # M65.133 - Planned Parenthood Assoc., San Francisco: Follow-up Studies of Patients Using IUCD's (Box 67, Folder 1193)
    - Grant # M65.134 - N.I.H. (U.S.): Motility and Energy Metabolism of Spermatozoa (Box 67, Folder 1194)
    - Grant # I65.135
      - Delivery Hospitals Several Countries: Postpartum Family Planning Program Background Papers (Box 67, Folder 1195-1196)
      - Delivery Hospitals Several Countries: Coordinated Program to Implement Family Planning (Box 67, Folder 1197-1199)
      - San Juan de Dios, Chile: Documentation (Box 67, Folder 1200)
      - San Juan de Dios, Chile: General Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 1201-1202)
      - San Juan de Dios, Chile: Narrative Reports (Box 67, Folder 1203-1204)
      - San Juan de Dios, Chile: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 67, Folder 1205)
      - San Juan de Dios, Chile: Purchasing (Box 67, Folder 1206-1207)
      - Family Planning Assoc., Hong Kong: Documentation (Box 67, Folder 1208-1209)
      - Family Planning Assoc., Hong Kong: General Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 1210-1211)
      - Family Planning Assoc., Hong Kong: Narrative Reports (Box 67, Folder 1212-1213)
      - Family Planning Assoc., Hong Kong: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 68, Folder 1214-1215)
      - Family Planning Assoc., Hong Kong: Purchasing (Box 68, Folder 1216)
      - S.A.T. Hospital, India: Documentation (Box 68, Folder 1217-1218)
      - S.A.T. Hospital, India: General Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 1219-1220)
      - S.A.T. Hospital, India: Evaluation (Box 68, Folder 1221)
      - S.A.T. Hospital, India: Narrative Reports (Box 68, Folder 1222-1223)
      - S.A.T. Hospital, India: Purchasing and Financial Reports (Box 68, Folder 1224)
      - University of Tokyo, Japan: Documentation (Box 68, Folder 1225)
      - University of Tokyo, Japan: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 68, Folder 1226-1227)
      - University of Tokyo, Japan: Narrative Reports (Box 68, Folder 1228-1229)
      - University of Tokyo, Japan: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 68, Folder 1230)
      - University of Tokyo, Japan: Purchasing (Box 68, Folder 1231-1232)
      - Hospital de la Mujer, Mexico: Documentation (Box 68, Folder 1233-1234)
      - Hospital de la Mujer, Mexico: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 68, Folder 1235-1236)
      - Hospital de la Mujer, Mexico: Narrative Reports (Box 68, Folder 1237)
      - Hospital de la Mujer, Mexico: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 68, Folder 1238)
      - Hospital de la Mujer, Mexico: Purchasing (Box 68, Folder 1239-1240)
      - Jinnah Central, Pakistan: Documentation (Box 68, Folder 1241-1242)
      - Jinnah Central, Pakistan: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 68, Folder 1243-1244)
      - Pakistan Post-partum: Documentation (Box 68, Folder 1245)
      - Pakistan Post-partum: General Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 1246)
      - Philippine General Hospital: Documentation (Box 68, Folder 1247-1248)
      - Philippine General Hospital: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 68, Folder 1249-1250)
      - Philippine General Hospital: Narrative Reports (Box 69, Folder 1251-1252)
      - Philippine General Hospital: Payments and Financial Statements (Box 69, Folder 1253)
      - Philippine General Hospital: Purchasing (Box 69, Folder 1254)
      - Population/Family Planning Div., Philippines: Family Planning Reporting System (Box 69, Folder 1255)
      - Population/Family Planning Div., Philippines: General Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 1256)